Athul Jayaram

in in/athuljayaram

SUMMARY

Experienced Application Security Engineer with a proven track record of safeguarding Fortune 500 companies applications and data for more than 5 years. Seeking the role of Security Engineer to protect organizations and their critical data assets.

EXPERIENCE

Founder

SecurityInfinity August 2020 - September 2023

· AI cloud cybersecurity suite for vulnerability scanning and real-time analytics.

Security Researcher

Bugcrowd

- · Performed NGPT for multiple customers of Bugcrowd
- · Bugcrowd MVP
- · Bugcrowd Top 100 Researcher

Security Engineer

Fuze

July 2019 - July 2022, Massachusetts, US

November 2017 - September 2023

- · Secured Fuze's cloud products including its web conferencing mobile apps, websites, APIs, server and User Data Storage.
- · Identified over 50 critical vulnerabilities protecting user data and brand reputation.
- · Coordinated with the IT and products team to launch products securely.

Cyber Risk Consultant

Deloitte

June 2018 - July 2019, India

- · Managed team of consultants and coordinated between Deloitte client and team.
- · Performed vulnerability assessment and penetration testing of critical assets.

Security Engineer Intern

LimeTray

September 2017 - November 2017

· Penetration Testing, Cloud Security, Vulnerability Assessment

Student Partner Intern

Microsoft

January 2017 - July 2017

· Software Development

EDUCATION

MBA in Operations and Marketing

Amity University • 2018

Bachelors in Computer Science Engineering

Amity University • 2013-17

CERTIFICATIONS

CEH

Safe Security · 2014

Foundations of Cybersecurity

Coursera · 2023

101 Reverse Engineering

US Department of Homeland Security

KET

University of Cambridge

SKILLS